("9 to 5" by Dolly Parton)
♪ Tumble out of bed ♪
♪ And stumble to the kitchen ♪
♪ Pour myself a cup of ambition ♪
♪ And yawn and stretch
and try to come to life ♪
♪ Jump in the shower ♪
♪ And the blood starts pumpin' ♪
♪ Out on the streets the
traffic starts jumpin' ♪
♪ For folks like me on
the job from 9 to 5 ♪
♪ Workin' 9 to 5 ♪
♪ What a way to make a livin' ♪
♪ Barely gettin' by ♪
♪ It's all takin' and no givin' ♪
♪ They just use your mind ♪
♪ And they never give you credit ♪
♪ It's enough to drive you ♪
♪ Crazy if you let it ♪
♪ 9 to 5 ♪
♪ For service and devotion ♪
♪ You would think that I ♪
♪ Would deserve a fat promotion ♪
♪ Want to move ahead ♪
♪ But the boss won't seem to let me ♪
♪ I swear sometimes that man is ♪
♪ Out to get me hmmm ♪
♪ They let you dream ♪
♪ Just a watch 'em shatter ♪
♪ You're just a step on
the boss man's ladder ♪
♪ But you got dreams
he'll never take away ♪
♪ In the same boat with
a lot of your friends ♪
♪ Waitin' for the day
your ship'll come in ♪
♪ And the tide's gonna turn ♪
♪ And it's all gonna roll you away ♪
♪ Workin' 9 to 5 ♪
♪ What a way to make livin' ♪
♪ Barely gettin' by ♪
♪ It's all takin' and no givin' ♪
♪ They just use your mind ♪
♪ And you never get the credit ♪
♪ It's enough to drive you ♪
♪ Crazy if you let it ♪
♪ 9 to 5 ♪
♪ Yeah they got you were they want you ♪
♪ There's a better life ♪
♪ And you think about it don't you ♪
♪ It's a rich man's game ♪
♪ No matter what they call it ♪
♪ And you spend your life ♪
♪ Putting money in his wallet ♪
♪ 9 to 5 ♪
♪ Oh what a way to make a livin' ♪
♪ Barely gettin' by ♪
♪ It's all takin' and no givin' ♪
♪ They just use your mind ♪
♪ And they never give you credit ♪
♪ It's enough to drive you ♪
♪ Crazy if you let it ♪
♪ 9 to 5 ♪
♪ Yeah they got you where they want you ♪
♪ There's a better life ♪
♪ And you dream about it don't you ♪